{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I have a book",
      "answer": "ich habe buch"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: He has a car",
      "answer": "er hat auto"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We have milk",
      "answer": "wir haben milch"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: She is student",
      "answer": "sie ist studentin"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: They are team",
      "answer": "sie sind mannschaft"
    },

    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I can play football",
      "answer": "ich kann fußball spielen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We can drink water",
      "answer": "wir können wasser trinken"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: He can cook pasta",
      "answer": "er kann pasta kochen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I want to eat bread",
      "answer": "ich will brot essen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: They want to read book",
      "answer": "sie wollen buch lesen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: You (du) must learn German",
      "answer": "du musst deutsch lernen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We must go home",
      "answer": "wir müssen nach hause gehen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: I should drink water",
      "answer": "ich soll wasser trinken"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: He should sleep",
      "answer": "er soll schlafen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: May I come in?",
      "answer": "darf ich reinkommen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: You (du) may eat apple",
      "answer": "du darfst apfel essen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: We may speak English",
      "answer": "wir dürfen englisch sprechen"
    }
  ]
}
